[{"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 2], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 2], [2, 1], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 3], [2, 1], [3, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0], [3, 3]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 3], [1, 2], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2], [3, 3]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 3], [2, 2], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 3], [2, 2], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 3], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 3], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 3], [3, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2], [3, 3]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 3], [3, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合2.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/组合4.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木10.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木3.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木4.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木2.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0], [3, 3]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}]